<?xml version='1.0' encoding='ISO-8859-1'?>

	<Items>
   		<entry>
            		<title>Drought Monitor</title>
			<questOne><![CDATA[<font size="2"><b><i>Does the land have enough water to sustain plants and animals?</i></b></font><p>Colors show experts' estimates of conditions related to dryness and drought. Categories reflect how much water is available in streams, lakes, and soils compared to usual for the time of year shown. The darker the shade on the map, the more severe the drought status. </p>]]></questOne>
			<questTwo><![CDATA[<font size="2"><b><i>What information do experts use to make these maps?</i></b></font><p>Each week, drought experts consider how recent precipitation totals compare to their long-term averages. They check temperatures, moisture levels in soils, and water levels in streams and lakes. They also watch for indicators of drought such as vegetation stress. Up to 300 people review the draft map to check it against reality. Each final map represents experts' best estimates of regional-scale drought conditions.</p>]]></questTwo>
			<aboutSnap>Colors show experts' estimates of conditions related to dryness and drought.</aboutSnap>
            		<imgURL>media/testMaps/usdroughtmonitor-weekly464.png</imgURL>
			<mapType>CONUS</mapType>
   		</entry>
   		<entry>
            		<title>Drought Outlook</title>
			<questOne><![CDATA[<font size="2"><b><i>How are conditions related to drought likely to change?</i></b></font><p>Colors show experts' estimates of how conditions related to drought are likely to change in the next month. Areas where experts expect below-average precipitation or above-average temperatures (which increases evaporation) may see drought develop, persist, or worsen. Areas with forecasts for above-average precipitation or below-average temperature may see drought conditions improve or end.</p>]]></questOne>
			<questTwo><![CDATA[<font size="2"><b><i>What information do experts use to produce drought outlooks?</i></b></font><p>Starting with knowledge of current drought status, experts examine weather forecasts and climate outlooks to estimate how much precipitation will fall and what temperatures will be over the next month. The experts consider seasonal patterns of precipitation (for example, if a region usually has a wet summer), and compare that information with forecasts to judge if conditions are likely to become drier or wetter.</p>]]></questTwo>
			<aboutSnap>Colors show experts' estimates of how conditions related to drought are likely to change in the next month.</aboutSnap>
            		<imgURL>media/testMaps/droughtoutlook-monthly460.png</imgURL>
			<mapType>CONUS</mapType>
   		</entry>
 	</Items>